asij.ac.jp 2017-07-09

# ASIJ Privacy Policy - The American School in Japan

**Use of Links**

Throughout our web pages, we provide links to other servers that may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained on other servers.

Creating a text link from your website to our site does not require permission.

**Use of Text and Images**

If you would like to publish information that you find on our website, please send your request to [webmaster@asij.ac.jp](mailto:webmaster@asij.ac.jp). Where text or images are posted on our site with the permission of the original copyright holder, a copyright statement appears at the bottom of the page.

All images and logos are the property of ASIJ or any credited author and may not be replicated in any fashion without prior consent. Information about using our logo and images is available from [communications@asij.ac.jp](mailto:communications@asij.ac.jp).

**Website Privacy Policy**

We have created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website.

  * **Reading or Downloading**  
We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or princeton.edu if you are connecting from Princeton University's domain), the date and time you access our site, and the internet address of the website from which you linked to our site.We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.  

  *   **Online Profile Updates and Donations  
** If you complete the Profile update form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the "Opt Out" section below.  

  * **Sending us an Email  
** You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer you questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.  

  * **Directories**  
Information provided by you that you opt to be included in any directories on our website, such as the alumni directory or mentoring/careers site, will be accessible to other members of our online community. This information is not accessible to the general public and you may opt in or out of these directories at any point. We may provide contact information to class agents, reunion organizers and other groups directly affiliated to ASIJ in order that they can contact you about events. Directories are provided for the personal and private use of ASIJ community members and information in school directories is not to be used for any type of marketing, direct mailing, commercial solicitations, promotions, chain mail, spamming, or the promotion of political agendas. Information contained in directories should not be posted to external sites or shared without the permission of the relevant individual.  

  * **Class Letters and Alumni News**  
You are invited to submit personal news items for publication on the website, class letters and The Ambassador magazine. Any information submitted will be accessible to members of your class, the online community and those on The Ambassador mailing lists. Some information from publicly available sources, such as newspapers and other websites maybe reprinted even when it has not been directly submitted by an individual. We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.If you sign up for one of our email lists, we will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. We won't share your name or email address with any outside parties. Your email may be shared with your class agent, reunion organizer or Alumni Council in order for them to contact you about special events and other items of potential interest. These groups should not use your email for any other purposes and if you receive inappropriate emails please forward them to [webmaster@asij.ac.jp](mailto:webmaster@asij.ac.jp). ASIJ reserves the right to terminate access to this site should any individual violate the privacy of another user.  

  * **Opt-Out or Change Your Contact Information**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us through a special [online form](https://www.asij.ac.jp/page.aspx?pid=188). You cannot remove yourself from our database, but you can prevent unwanted communication should you desire. You can also change your contact information using the alumni profile or through MOL for current parents.
